https://www.e2g.com/privacy-policy/

eec WebTools UsersE2G News216.283.9519Contact UsPriority Support Search
Search
Problems. Solved.How Do I Capture Corporate Memory?How Do I Implement a Mechanical Integrity Program?How Do I Optimize My Inspections?I Have Unanticipated Damage.
Now What?Is My Facility Code Compliant?Should I Run, Repair, or Replace?Where Should I Start?What are My Design Requirements?Consulting ServicesAdvanced AnalysisAdvanced Analysis for the Nuclear IndustryAdvanced Stress AnalysisComputational Fluid DynamicsFlange Evaluation & OptimizationHigh-Temperature SolutionsFitness-For-ServiceCivil & Structural Engineering ServicesEquipment Design & RepairEquipment-Specific SolutionsField ServicesMechanical IntegrityBrittle Fracture ScreeningMaterials & CorrosionCCD-IOW – PetrochemicalCCD-IOW – RefineryDamage Mechanism ReviewsFailure AnalysisHeater Tube Remaining Life EvaluationsHot Tap AssessmentsOmega Creep TestingWeld RepairPipeline ServicesPressure Relief & Process DesignRelief System 3rd Party QA/QCRelief System & Flare Header AnalysisHeat Exchanger Tube Rupture AnalysisInlet Pressure Drop & the 3% RulePressure Relief Device Mechanical IntegrityProcess Design & SimulationPHAs & LOPAsPressure Relief/PSM AuditingRisk-Based InspectionHeat Exchanger BundlesPressure Relief DevicesRisk-Based Inspection Implementation & Ongoing Program ManagementRotating Equipment, Vibration, & DynamicsAcoustic VibrationPiping & Structural VibrationRotating ServicesEquity Engineering Practices®Software & ToolsAPI RBI SoftwareDamagePlus™ SoftwarePlantManager™ SoftwareSagePlus™ Analytical Software30-Day Purchase Optionseec WebToolsAPI 579 / ASME FFSDamage WebHotTapIntelliJointSIMFLEX-IIIeec WebTool SuiteseecPlantEngineer SuiteeecPlantInspector SuiteeecTurnaround Suiteeec WebTool SuiteseecFatigueAnalysis SuiteeecPipeline SuiteeecMaterials SuiteeecInspectionService SuiteTraining & EventsAPI UniversityDamage MechanismsFitness-For-ServicePressure Relieving SystemsRisk-Based InspectionE²G Technical Institute (ETI)API RBI SoftwareIntroduction to Instrumentation & Process ControlIntroduction to Welding EngineeringIntroduction to Materials EngineeringPressure Vessels: ASME VIII-1Pressure Vessels: ASME VIII-2Pressure Vessels: Design by Analysis MethodsProcess PipingSagePlus™ SoftwareStorage TanksEvent CalendarWebinarsAbout UsCareersHistoryLibraryMeet Our ExpertsPhilanthropic EndeavorsPriority Support E2G is available to contact for priority support services:Contact E2G
loading...
PRIVACY POLICY FOR THE EQUITY ENGINEERING GROUP’S WEBSITEPLEASE READ THIS PRIVACY POLICY CAREFULLY BEFORE USING THIS WEBSITE.Our Thoughts on PrivacyThe operator of this website (the “Website”), namely, The Equity Engineering Group, Inc. (“E2G” or “we,” “us,” or “our”), has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate its commitment to privacy.  We urge you to read this complete privacy policy to learn the practices and procedures we follow relating to your online privacy.What This Privacy Policy CoversThis privacy policy will tell you the type of information that is collected about you when you use this Website, how the information is collected, what the information will be used for, and to whom it will be given.  This privacy policy will also explain how to limit our use of your personal information.Contact the WEBSITEThe Website is the responsibility of E2G.  If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the Website, or your use of the Website, you can contact us by email at Privacy@e2g.com or by U.S. Mail at The Equity Engineering Group, Inc., 20600 Chagrin Boulevard, Suite 1200, Shaker Heights, Ohio 44122.  You can reach us by phone at (216) 658-1093.What Kind of Personal Information E2G CollectsThe privacy and security of your information are important to us.  We give you the option of signing up to receive email updates.  If you choose to register with us, we will need your name and email address.  We take care to protect the online data you submit to us when using the Website and store such information in a secure database.Also, some information about your server address, web browser, and computer system are transmitted to our web servers so we can operate and improve the Website.  For example, we track the number of people who view each page and other information to determine the most popular features and to refine our design and marketing efforts.  We collect and store such information on an aggregated basis.To provide the services offered at the Website, we reserve the right to collect and track:The home server, IP addresses and domain names, email addresses, type of computer, and type of web browser you are using while you visit the WebsiteOther information that you volunteer when you use the WebsiteHow We Use Your Personal InformationWe send to your email address updates about new services or support requests or about a material change to this privacy policy or the Terms and Conditions, or to comply with the law or legal process served on E2G.Aggregated Uses of Information:We use IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our server and to administer the Website, to authenticate user accounts, and to gather broad demographic information.We use demographic and profile data only for personalized content and statistical information and do not share those data with other companies except in ways that do not identify our users. We use these data to tailor the visitor’s experience at the Website, showing you content that we think might interest you and displaying the content according to your preferences.Users may opt out of receiving future mailings at any time.  Please see the “Opting Out” section below for more information.E2G will not share your email address with anyone else, except that E2G may disclose information about its users if required to do so by law or to respond to subpoenas, court orders, or other legal processes.  We may also disclose information about users to law enforcement officers or others if reasonably necessary to enforce its terms of use, to respond to claims that any posting or other content violates the rights of third parties, or to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of E2G, its users, or the general public.SecurityThe security of our users’ personally identifying information is of great concern to us.  Although perfect security does not exist in any transaction process online or in stores, the Website has security measures in place to protect against the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control.  Please be assured that we are constantly reviewing our security processes to keep up to date with the highest levels of security encryption and service.CookiesA “cookie” is a small file sent from a web server to your browser and is stored on your computer’s hard drive when you visit certain websites.  Cookies help web surfing by saving visitor preferences and other information.  The use of cookies is a widespread industry standard and many websites use cookies.Most web browsers are initially configured to accept and process cookies.  You can configure your browser to refuse cookies.E2G uses cookies to keep track of your logged-in status.  We reserve the right to use cookies to customize content based on the pages you have looked at.  If you have any questions concerning our use of cookies, please contact us at Privacy@e2g.com.Opting OutThe Website provides users the opportunity to opt out of receiving communications from us at the point where we request information about the users.  You can send your request by email to Privacy@e2g.com, by phone at (216) 658-1093, or by U.S. Mail at The Equity Engineering Group, Inc., 20600 Chagrin Boulevard, Suite 1200, Shaker Heights, Ohio 44122, in order to unsubscribe from any or all email lists.Requesting to See Your Personal InformationYou may request via email, telephone, or U.S. Mail that we provide you with the personal information we have concerning you.  Once you receive this information, you may request that we modify or remove any of your personal information.  We reserve the right to verify your identity before sending you this information.CALIFORNIA RESIDENTSResidents of California, thanks to section 1798.83 of the California Civil Code, may request once per calendar year, from companies conducting business in California a list of all third parties to whom the company has disclosed certain personally identifiable information as defined under California law during the preceding year for third-party direct marketing purposes.  In your request, please attest to your being a California resident and provide a current California address for our response.If you are a California resident and under the age of 18, and a registered user of this Website, section 22581 of the California Business and Professions Code permits you to request and obtain the removal of content that you have publicly posted.  Please note that your request will not ensure a complete removal of the content and that in some cases the statute may not require or allow removal even if requested.Notice about the European Union’s General Data Protection Regulations (GDPR)You may have certain rights under the European Union’s GDPR 2016/679.  The GDPR is a complex regulatory scheme and we do not intend to provide every detail here.  If interested, you should read the GDPR and the relevant guidance provided by the applicable authorities for a fuller explanation.The GDPR provides the right, where applicable, to (a) access, (b) publication, (c) erasure, (d) restrict processing, (e) object to processing, (f) data portability, (g) complain to a supervisory authority, and (h) withdraw consent.Where applicable, the GDPR provides you the right to confirm whether E2G has processed your Personal Data (as defined in the GDPR) and to access those data together with certain other information including the purposes of the processing, the categories of Personal Data concerned, and the recipients of the Personal Data.  Where applicable, and providing that we do not affect the rights and freedoms of anyone else, we will supply you with one copy of your Personal Data.  The first copy is free.  We may charge a reasonable fee for additional copies.Where applicable, the GDPR provides you the rights to rectify any inaccurate Personal Data about you and, taking into account the purposes of the processing, to complete any incomplete data about you.In some circumstances, the GDPR provides you the right to erase your Personal Data without undue delay, including when we no longer need the Personal Data for the purposes for which we collected or processed the Personal Data, if you withdraw your consent to consent-based processing, if you object to the processing of the Personal Data under certain rules of the GDPR, if the processing is for the purpose of direct marketing, and if the Personal Data have been unlawfully processed.  However, the GDPR provides exceptions or exclusions to the right to erase, including where the processing is necessary for the exercise of free expression and information, to comply with a legal obligation, or to establish, exercise, or defend a legal claim.In some circumstances, the GDPR provides you the right to restrict the processing of your Personal Data, such as to contest the accuracy of the Personal Data, where the processing is unlawful but you oppose erasure, or when we no longer need the Personal Data for the purpose of our processing but you require Personal Data to establish, exercise, or defend a legal claim, and you have objected to the processing pending the verification of that objection.  When processing has been restricted on this basis, we may continue to store your Personal Data, but we will process your data otherwise only with your consent, to establish, exercise, or defend a legal claim, to protect another natural or legal person’s rights, or for reasons of important public interest.If applicable, the GDPR provides the right to object to our processing of your Personal Data on grounds relating to your situation, but only to the extent that the processing is necessary for a task carried out in the public interest or to exercise any official authority vested in E2G, or for a legitimate interest pursued by E2G or someone else.  If you object, we shall stop processing the Personal Data unless we can demonstrate compelling legitimate grounds to process the information that override your interests, rights, and freedoms, or the purpose of the processing is to establish, exercise, or defend a legal claim.You may object to our processing of your Personal Data for direct marketing purposes including profiling for direct marketing purposes.  If you notify us of such an objection, we shall stop processing your Personal Data for that purpose.You may object to our processing of your Personal Data for scientific or historical research or statistical purposes on grounds relating to your particular situation, unless the processing is necessary for a task carried out in the public interest.If the legal basis for our processing your Personal Data is consent or that the processing is necessary to perform a contract to which you are a party, or in order to take steps at your request before entering into a contract, and such processing is carried out by automatic means, you have the right to receive your Personal Data from us in a structured, commonly used, and machine-readable format.  But this right does not apply when its application will adversely affect the rights and freedoms of others.If you believe that our processing of your Personal Data infringes any data-protection statute, rule, or regulation, you may lodge a complaint with the appropriate authorities responsible for data protection.  If applicable, you may lodge that complaint in the European Union member state of your habitual residence, your workplace, or the place of the alleged infringement.To the extent that we base our processing of your Personal Data on your consent, you may withdraw that consent at any time, but your withdrawal of that consent will not affect the lawfulness of any processing we do before your withdrawal.If applicable, you may exercise any of your rights in relation to your Personal Data by emailing E2G at Privacy@e2g.com.Access to ChildrenWe do not direct any features of the Website to children under the age of 13.  Children under 13 may not register with E2G or download, install, or use any of the services available on the Website.  Products and services for sale are intended for purchase by adults.  By making a purchase on the Website, you agree that you are at least 13 years of age.E2G and this Website will…NOT collect personally identifiable offline contact information from children under the age of 13 without prior parental consent.NOT distribute to third parties any personally identifiable information with respect to children under the age of 13 without prior parental consent.NOT give the ability to post publicly or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information with respect to children under the age of 13 without prior parental consent.NOT entice children under the age of 13 by the prospect of a special game, prize, or other activity to divulge more information than is needed to participate in the activity.Changes to This Privacy PolicyWe reserve the right to change this policy at any time.  We ask that you review this privacy policy from time to time to ensure you are familiar with the most current version of it.Acceptance of This Privacy PolicyBy visiting or otherwise using the Website, you agree to the terms as well as any posted changes of this privacy policy.  By visiting or otherwise using the Website, you hereby consent to the collection and use of this information by E2G.  If you do not so agree, DO NOT use the Website.Date of last update: May 15, 2020CIN2000:2730735v1 35783.00004Upcoming Training Sessions CalendarE2G has a full calendar of upcoming events. Visit it to see our entire schedule. View Full Calendar E2G Help Desk ServicesOur Help Desk IT specialists and engineers are available for questions about all E2G products. Our goal is to facilitate upgrades and conversions, quickly answer your questions, and help you benefit from our state-of-the-art software products.
216.658.4777Weekdays 9am – 4pm ET
HelpDesk@E2G.com Full Name
Your Company
Phone Number
Email Address
Inquiry Type (optional) Select an Inquiry TypeSoftware SupportSoftware PurchaseConsulting Services SupportTraining & Events SupportGeneral Inquiry Message
Send MessageConnect With E2G 216.283.9519Require expert support? Call E2G today and we’ll resolve your problem. Follow E2G on LinkedInFollow us on LinkedIn for current E2G news, upcoming training sessions, presentation overviews, and more.
E2G Industry NewsletterStay Up to Date With the Latest Industry News & Tips. Email Address
Sign Up TodayHomeProblems. Solved.How Do I Capture Corporate Memory?How Do I Implement a Mechanical Integrity Program?How Do I Optimize My Inspections?I Have Unanticipated Damage.
Now What?Is My Facility Code Compliant?Should I Run, Repair, or Replace?What are My Design Requirements?Where Should I Start?Privacy
PolicyConsulting ServicesAdvanced AnalysisAdvanced Analysis for the Nuclear IndustryAdvanced Stress AnalysisComputational Fluid DynamicsFlange Evaluation & OptimizationHigh-Temperature SolutionsFitness-For-ServiceCivil & Structural Engineering ServicesEquipment-Specific SolutionsEquipment Design & RepairField ServicesMechanical IntegrityBrittle Fracture ScreeningMaterials & CorrosionCCD-IOW – PetrochemicalCCD-IOW – RefineryDamage Mechanism ReviewsFailure AnalysisHeater Tube Remaining Life EvaluationsHot Tap AssessmentsOmega Creep TestingWeld RepairPipeline ServicesConsulting ServicesPressure Relief & Process DesignRelief System & Flare Header AnalysisHeat Exchanger Tube Rupture AnalysisPressure Relief Device Mechanical IntegrityProcess Design & SimulationPHAs & LOPAsPressure Relief/PSM AuditingRisk-Based InspectionHeat Exchanger (HE) BundlesPressure Relief DevicesRisk-Based Inspection Implementation & Ongoing Program ManagementRotating Equipment, Vibration, & DynamicsPiping & Structural VibrationRotating ServicesEquity Engineering Practices®Software & ToolsAPI RBI SoftwareDamagePlus™PlantManager™SagePlus™SIMFLEX-IIIeec WebToolsAPI 579 / ASME FFSDamage WebHotTapIntelliJointeec WebTools SuiteseecFatigueAnalysis SuiteeecInspectionService SuiteeecMaterials SuiteeecPipeline SuiteeecPlantInspector SuiteeecPlantEngineer SuiteeecTurnaround SuiteTraining & EventsAPI UniversityDamage MechanismsRisk-Based InspectionPressure Relieving SystemsFitness-For-ServiceE²G Technical Institute (ETI)API RBI SoftwareIntroduction to Instrumentation & Process ControlIntroduction to Materials EngineeringIntroduction to Welding EngineeringPressure Vessels: ASME VIII-1Pressure Vessels: ASME VIII-2Pressure Vessels: Design by Analysis MethodsProcess PipingSagePlus™ SoftwareStorage TanksEvent CalendarWebinarsContact UsAbout UsCareersHistoryLibraryMeet Our ExpertsPhilanthropic EndeavorsShaker Heights, Ohio20600 Chagrin Boulevard | Suite 1200 Shaker Heights, OH 44122P: 216.283.9519 | F: 216.283.6022E: CustomerService@E2G.comHouston, Texas2625 Bay Area Boulevard | Suite 325 Houston, TX 77058P: 281.480.0556 | F: 281.480.2063E: CustomerService@E2G.com E2G|The Equity Engineering Group, Inc. is certified to the ISO 9001:2015 quality standard by ASR.© 2019 E2G|The Equity Engineering Group, Inc.
